Finding Aid for the William and Lee Bell Scripts for Television Soap Operas PASC.0096
UCLA Library Special Collections
William and Lee Bell scripts for television soap operas
1958-circa 1997
UCLA Library Special Collections
Seeger, Charles
PASC.0096
727 linear feet (1454 boxes)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942340003606533
Biography
William and Lee Phillip Bell were born and raised in Chicago, IL; the couple married in 1954; William J. began his writing career (1956) on "Guiding Light," wrote for "As The World Turns," co-created "Another World" (1964) with Irna Phillips, and began writing for "Days Of Our Lives" (1966); he is executive producer, co-creator and head writer for both "The Bold And The Beautiful" and "The Young And The Restless"; Lee Bell graduated Northwestern Univ. with a BS in Microbiology, 1950; she began hosting her own afternoon talk show (1954) and went on to co-create "The Bold And The Beautiful" and "The Young And The Restless"; she is the recipient of numerous awards and is president of Bell-Phillip TV Productions.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of various versions of scripts for soap operas such as "The Bold And The Beautiful," "Days Of Our Lives," and "The Young And The Restless." Also includes production material and correspondence.
Organization
Arranged in the following series:
All My Children
Another World
As The World Turns
The Bold And The Beautiful
Days Of Our Lives
The Guiding Light
Laura
Love Is A Many Splendored Thing
The Many Ways Of Love
Our Private World
The Young And The Restless
Composers -- United States.; Young And The Restless (Television program).; Bold And The Beautiful (Television program).; Days of Our Lives (Television program).; Music teachers -- United States.; Musicologists -- United States -- Archives.; Seeger, Charles, 1886-1979--Archives.; Bell, William J.; Bell, Lee Phillip
- ALL MY CHILDREN
  - Aired: NOT DATED.. Notes: SERIES IDEA. (Box 130)
- ANOTHER WORLD
  - Aired: 11/27/64-01/06/72. Notes: SCRIPT; PRODUCTION MATERIAL FOR SERIES (INCL. SALE CONTRACT). (Box 130)
  - Prod. #549-574. Aired: 07/29/66-08/11/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 131)
  - Prod. #575-602. Aired: 08/24/66-09/30/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 132)
  - Prod. #603-626. Aired: 10/03/66-11/04/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 133)
  - Prod. #627-651. Aired: 11/07/66-12/13/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 134)
  - Prod. #652-675. Aired: 12/14/67-01/17/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 135)
  - Prod. #676-699. Aired: 01/18/67-02/25/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 136)
  - Prod. #700-724. Aired: 02/23/67-03/29/67. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 137)
  - Prod. #725-746. Aired: 03/30/67-05/11/67. Notes: SCRIPTS (TO END). (Box 138)
  - Prod. #1-95. Aired: 05/04/64-09/15/64. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 195)
  - Prod. #96-123. Aired: 09/16/64-10/30/64. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 196)
  - Prod. #124-205. Aired: 11/02/64-02/26/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 197)
  - Prod. #206-235. Aired: 03/01/65-04/13/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 198)
  - Prod. #236-260. Aired: 04/14/65-05/18/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 199)
  - Prod. #261-290. Aired: 05/19/65-06/30/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 200)
  - Prod. #291-316. Aired: 07/01/65-08/06/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 201)
  - Prod. #317-346. Aired: 08/09/65-09/17/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 202)
  - Prod. #347-370. Aired: 09/20/65-10/21/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 203)
  - Prod. #371-398. Aired: 10/22/65-12/08/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 204)
  - Prod. #399-423. Aired: 12/09/65-01/03/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 205)
  - Prod. #424-448. Aired: 01/04/66-02/17/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 206)
  - Prod. #452-477. Aired: 02/28/66-04/16/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 207)
  - Prod. #478-504. Aired: 04/07/66-05/13/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 208)
  - Prod. #505-526. Aired: 05/17/66-06/01/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 209)
  - Prod. #527-548. Aired: 06/16/66-07/01/66. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 210)
- AS THE WORLD TURNS
  - Prod. #66/1-9. Aired: 01/03/66-09/22/66. Notes: SCRIPTS (INCOMPLETE). (Box 139)
  - Prod. #58/1-6. Aired: 06/02/58-10/22/58. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 140)
  - Prod. #58/7-12. Aired: 07/31/58-12/01/58. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 141)
  - Prod. #65/1-5. Aired: 01/04/65-05/21/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 145)
  - Prod. #65/6-9. Aired: 06/01/65-09/13/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 146)
  - Prod. #65/9-12. Aired: 09/14/65-12/31/65. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 147)
  - Prod. #64/1-6. Aired: 01/02/64-06/30/64. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 148)
  - Prod. #64/7-12. Aired: 07/01/64-12/30/64. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 149)
  - Prod. #63/1-5. Aired: 01/02/63-05/31/63. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 150)
  - Prod. #63/6-12. Aired: 06/03/63-12/31/63. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 151)
  - Prod. #62/1-7. Aired: 01/02/62-07/31/62. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 152)
  - Prod. #62/8-12. Aired: 08/14/62-12/31/62. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 153)
  - Prod. #61/1-6. Aired: 01/03/61-05/16/61. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 154)
  - Prod. #61/7-12. Aired: 07/31/61-12/29/61. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 155)
  - Prod. #60/1-5. Aired: 01/04/60-05/31/60. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 156)
  - Prod. #60/6-12. Aired: 06/01/60-12/30/60. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 157)
  - Prod. #59/1-6. Aired: 01/30/59-06/03/59. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 158)
  - Prod. #59/7-12. Aired: 07/01/59-12/25/59. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 159)
  - Prod. #481-501. Aired: 02/03/58-03/03/58. (Box 753)
- BOLD AND THE BEAUTIFUL, THE
  - Prod. #83-103. Aired: 07/15/87-08/18/87. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 350)
  - Prod. #104-123. Aired: (TAPE)07/27/87-09/25/87. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 351)
  - Prod. #124-144. Aired: 09/28/87-10/26/87. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 352)
  - Prod. #145-165. Aired: 10/27/87-11/24/87. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 353)
  - Prod. #166-186. Aired: 11/25/87-12/28/87. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 354)
  - Prod. #187-207. Aired: 12/29/87-01/29/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 355)
  - Prod. #208-228. Aired: 02/01/88-03/01/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 356)
  - Prod. #229-249. Aired: 03/02/88-03/23/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 357)
  - Prod. #250-270. Aired: 03/31/88-04/28/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 358)
  - Prod. #271-291. Aired: 04/23/88-05/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 359)
  - Prod. #292-312. Aired: 05/30/88-06/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 360)
  - Prod. #313-333. Aired: 06/28/88-07/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 361)
  - Prod. #334-354. Aired: 07/27/88-08/24/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 362)
  - Prod. #355-375. Aired: 08/25/88-09/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 363)
  - Prod. #376-396. Aired: 09/27/88-10/26/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 364)
  - Prod. #397-417. Aired: 10/26/88-11/23/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 365)
  - Prod. #418-438. Aired: 11/28/88-12/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 366)
  - Prod. #439-459. Aired: 12/28/88-01/27/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 367)
  - Prod. #460-480. Aired: 01/30/89-02/28/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 368)
  - Prod. #481-501. Aired: 03/01/89-03/28/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 369)
  - Prod. #502-522. Aired: 03/30/89-04/27/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 370)
  - Prod. #523-543. Aired: 04/28/89-05/26/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 371)
  - Prod. #544-564. Aired: 05/29/89-06/26/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 372)
  - Prod. #565-585. Aired: 06/27/89-07/25/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 373)
  - Prod. #586-606. Aired: 07/26/89-08/23/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 374)
  - Prod. #607-627. Aired: 08/24/89-09/25/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 375)
  - Prod. #628-648. Aired: 09/26/89-10/24/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 376)
  - Prod. #649-669. Aired: 10/25/89-11/22/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 377)
  - Prod. #670-690. Aired: 11/27/89-12/26/89. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 378)
  - Prod. #691-711. Aired: 12/27/89-01/25/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 379)
  - Prod. #712-732. Aired: 01/26/90-02/26/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 380)
  - Prod. #733-753. Aired: 02/27/90-03/27/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 381)
  - Prod. #754-774. Aired: 03/28/90-04/25/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 382)
  - Prod. #775-795. Aired: 04/26/90-05/24/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 383)
  - Prod. #796-816. Aired: 05/25/90-06/22/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 384)
  - Prod. #817-839. Aired: 06/25/90-07/24/90. Notes: SCRIPTS (MISSING 0835). (Box 385)
  - Prod. #839-858. Aired: 07/25/90-08/21/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 386)
  - Prod. #859-879. Aired: 08/21/90-09/21/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 387)
  - Prod. #880-897. Aired: 09/24/90-11/17/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 388)
  - Prod. #898-915. Aired: 11/18/90-11/12/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 389)
  - Prod. #916-935. Aired: 11/13/90-12/12/90. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 390)
  - Prod. #936-953. Aired: 12/13/90-01/09/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 391)
  - Prod. #954-971. Aired: 01/10/91-02/05/91. Notes: (MISSING 969). (Box 392)
  - Prod. #972-992. Aired: 02/06/91-03/08/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 393)
  - Prod. #993-1013. Aired: 03/11/91-04/12/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 394)
  - Prod. #1014-1032. Aired: 04/15/91-05/09/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 395)
  - Prod. #1033-1050. Aired: 05/10/91-06/04/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 396)
  - Prod. #1051-1068. Aired: 05/10/91-06/28/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 397)
  - Prod. #1069-1086. Aired: 07/01/91-07/24/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 398)
  - Prod. #1087-1105. Aired: 07/25/91-08/20/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 399)
  - Prod. #1106-1122. Aired: 08/21/91-09/16/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 400)
  - Prod. #1123-1140. Aired: 09/17/91-11/10/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 401)
  - Prod. #1141-1160. Aired: 10/11/91-11/07/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 402)
  - Prod. #1161-1180. Aired: 11/11/91-12/09/91. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 403)
  - Prod. #1181-1203. Aired: 12/10/91-01/13/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 404)
  - Prod. #1204-1226. Aired: 01/14/92-02/13/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 405)
  - Prod. #1227-1247. Aired: 02/14/92-03/16/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 406)
  - Prod. #1248-1257. Aired: 03/17/92-04/01/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 598)
  - Prod. #1258-1278. Aired: 04/02/92-04/30/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 599)
  - Prod. #1279-1300. Aired: 05/01/92-06/01/92. Notes: SCRIPTS (#1289 MISSING). (Box 600)
  - Prod. #1301-1314. Aired: 06/02/92-06/19/92. Notes: Missing # 1315-1321. (Box 601)
  - Prod. #1322-1331. Aired: 07/01/92-07/14/92. Notes: Missing # 1323, 1324, 1328. (Box 601)
  - Prod. #1333-1363. Aired: 07/16/92-08/27/92. Notes: Missing # 1332, 1346-1353. (Box 602)
  - Prod. #1364-1384. Aired: 08/28/92-09/29/92. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 603)
  - Prod. #1385-1412. Aired: 09/30/92-11/06/92. Notes: Missing # 1406-1408, #413-1420. (Box 604)
  - Prod. #1421-1446. Aired: 11/19/92-12/28/92. Notes: Missing # 1424, 1425, 1430, 1431. (Box 605)
  - Prod. #1447-1470. Aired: 12/29/92-02/02/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 606)
  - Prod. #1471-1493. Aired: 02/03/93-03/05/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 607)
  - Prod. #1494-1516. Aired: 03/08/93-04/09/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 608)
  - Prod. #1517-1526. Aired: 04/12/93-04/23/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 609)
  - Prod. #1750-1767. Aired: 03/10/94-04/06/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 633)
  - Prod. #1768-1786. Aired: 04/07/94-05/03/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 634)
  - Prod. #1787-1802. Aired: 05/04/94-05/25/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 635)
  - Prod. #1803-1809. Aired: 05/26/94-06/03/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 636)
  - Prod. #1810-1825. Aired: 06/06/94-06/27/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 637)
  - Prod. #1826-1840. Aired: 06/28/94-07/18/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 638)
  - Prod. #1841-1855. Aired: 07/19/94-08/16/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 639)
  - Prod. #1856-1869. Aired: 08/17/94-09/07/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 640)
  - Prod. #1870-1884. Aired: 09/08/94-09/29/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 641)
  - Prod. #1519-1531. Aired: 04/14/93-04/30/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 642)
  - Prod. #1597-1616. Aired: 08/02/93-08/21/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 643)
  - Aired:. Notes: Set drawings, first season. (Box 644)
  - Aired:. Notes: Information on shares, May-June 1987. (Box 644)
  - Aired:. Notes: Audition materials, 1986/1987. (Box 644)
  - Prod. #1. Aired:. Notes: Story outline "Rags", Jan. 1986, William Bell. - Working draft #1. (Box 644)
  - Prod. #1617-1631. Aired: 08/20/93-09/21/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 645)
  - Prod. #1632-1650. Aired: 09/22/93-10/18/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 646)
  - Prod. #1651-1670. Aired: 10/19/93-11/15/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 647)
  - Prod. #1885-1896. Aired: 09/30/94-10/18/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 648)
  - Prod. #1532-1546. Aired: 05/03/93-05/21/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 649)
  - Prod. #1547-1561. Aired: 05/24/93-06/11/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 650)
  - Prod. #1562-1576. Aired: 06/14/93-07/02/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 651)
  - Prod. #1577-1592. Aired: 07/05/93-07/26/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 652)
  - Prod. #1593-1596. Aired: 07/27/93-07/30/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 653)
  - Prod. #1671-1676. Aired: 11/16/93-11/23/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 663)
  - Prod. #1677-1691. Aired: 11/24/93-12/15/93. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 664)
  - Prod. #1692-1706. Aired: 12/16/93-01/05/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 665)
  - Prod. #1707-1721. Aired: 01/06/94-01/26/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 666)
  - Prod. #1722-1737. Aired: 01/27/94-02/18/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 667)
  - Prod. #1738-1749. Aired: 02/22/94-03/09/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 668)
  - Prod. #1897-1919. Aired: 10/25/94-11/20/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 724)
  - Prod. #1920-1939. Aired: 11/21/94-12/19/94. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 725)
  - Prod. #1940-1960. Aired: 12/20/94-01/10/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 726)
  - Prod. #1961-1979. Aired: 01/19/95-02/15/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 727)
  - Prod. #1980-1998. Aired: 02/16/95-03/20/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 728)
  - Prod. #1999-2020. Aired: 03/21/95-04/19/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 729)
  - Prod. #2021-2043. Aired: 04/20/95-05/22/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 730)
  - Prod. #2044-2067. Aired: 05/24/95-06/26/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 731)
  - Prod. #2068-2089. Aired: 06/27/95-07/26/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 732)
  - Prod. #2090-2109. Aired: 07/27/95-08/18/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 733)
  - Prod. #2110-2129. Aired: 08/24/95-09/22/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 734)
  - Prod. #2130-2149. Aired: 09/25/95-10/20/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 735)
  - Prod. #2150-2157. Aired: 10/23/95-11/02/95. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 736)
  - Prod. #2343-2348. Aired: 07/26/96-08/02/96. (Box 806)
  - Prod. #2349-2366. Aired: 08/05/96-08/21/96. (Box 807)
  - Prod. #2367-2384. Aired: 08/08/96-09/25/96. (Box 808)
  - Prod. #2385-2401. Aired: 09/26/96-10/18/96. (Box 809)
  - Prod. #2402-2419. Aired: 10/21/96-11/13/96. (Box 810)
  - Prod. #2420-2437. Aired: 11/14/96-12/03/06. (Box 811)
  - Prod. #2438-2455. Aired: 12/11/96-01/07/97. (Box 812)
  - Prod. #2456-2473. Aired: 01/08/97-01/31/97. (Box 813)
  - Prod. #2474-2491. Aired: 02/03/97-02/27/97. (Box 814)
  - Prod. #2492-2510. Aired: 03/07/97-03/28/97. (Box 815)
  - Prod. #2511-2526. Aired: 03/31/97-04/21/97. (Box 816)
  - Prod. #2527-2546. Aired: 04/22/97-05/19/97. (Box 817)
  - Prod. #2547-2562. Aired: 05/20/97-06/10/97. (Box 818)
  - Prod. #2563-2580. Aired: 06/11/97-07/04/97. (Box 819)
  - Prod. #2581-2598. Aired: 07/07/97-07/30/97. (Box 820)
  - Prod. #2599-2605. Aired: 07/31/97-08/08/97. (Box 821)
  - Prod. #1-25. Aired: 03/23/87-04/24/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 822)
  - Prod. #26-49. Aired: 04/27/87-05/28087. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 823)
  - Prod. #50-72. Aired: 05/29/87-06/30/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 824)
  - Prod. #73-89. Aired: 06/01/87-06/23/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 825)
  - Prod. #90-111. Aired: 07/24/87-TBA (09/03/87). Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 826)
  - Prod. #112-133. Aired: TBA (08/06/87)-10/09/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (tape/airdates). (Box 827)
  - Prod. #134-155. Aired: 10/12/87-11/10/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 828)
  - Prod. #156-178. Aired: 11/11/87-12/16/87. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 829)
  - Prod. #179-200. Aired: 12/17/87-01/19/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 830)
  - Prod. #201-224. Aired: 01/20/88-02/23/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 831)
  - Prod. #225-248. Aired: 02/25/88-03/28/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 832)
  - Prod. #249-265. Aired: 03/29/88-04/20/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 833)
  - Prod. #266-291. Aired: 04/21/88-05/27/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 834)
  - Prod. #292-319. Aired: 05/30/88-07/06/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 835)
  - Prod. #320-348. Aired: 07/07/88-08/16/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 836)
  - Prod. #349-374. Aired: 08/17/88-09/22/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 837)
  - Prod. #375-396. Aired: 09/25/88-10/24/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 838)
  - Prod. #397-420. Aired: 10/26/88-11/30/88. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 839)
  - Prod. #421-447. Aired: 12/01/88-01/10/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 840)
  - Prod. #448-474. Aired: 01/11/89-02/17/89. Notes: SCRIPTS SCRIPTS (Missing #454). (Box 841)
  - Prod. #475-500. Aired: 02/20/89-03/28/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 842)
  - Prod. #501-530. Aired: 03/29/89-05/08/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 843)
  - Prod. #531-560. Aired: 05/09/89-06/20/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 844)
  - Prod. #561-590. Aired: 06/21/89-08/01/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 845)
  - Prod. #591-620. Aired: 08/02/89-09/14/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 846)
  - Prod. #621-648. Aired: 09/15/89-10/24/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 847)
  - Prod. #649-678. Aired: 10/25/89-12/07/89. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 848)
  - Prod. #679-709. Aired: 12/08/89-01/22/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 849)
  - Prod. #710-740. Aired: 01/23/90-03/05/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 850)
  - Prod. #741-770. Aired: 03/06/90-04/19/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 851)
  - Prod. #771-798. Aired: 04/20/90-05/27/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 852)
  - Prod. #799-827. Aired: 05/28/90-07/10/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 853)
  - Prod. #828-858. Aired: 07/11/90-08/14/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 854)
  - Prod. #859-890. Aired: 08/15/90-10/08/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 855)
  - Prod. #891-920. Aired: 10/09/90-11/19/90. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 856)
  - Prod. #921-950. Aired: 11/20/90-01/04/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 857)
  - Prod. #951-980. Aired: 01/07/91-02/19/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 858)
  - Prod. #981-1010. Aired: 02/20/91-04/04/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #992). (Box 859)
  - Prod. #1011-1040. Aired: 04/10/91-05/21/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 860)
  - Prod. #1041-1070. Aired: 05/22/91-07/02/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 861)
  - Prod. #1071-1100. Aired: 07/03/91-08/13/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 862)
  - Prod. #1101-1129. Aired: 08/14/91-09/25/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 863)
  - Prod. #1130-1159. Aired: 09/26/91-11/06/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 864)
  - Prod. #1160-1189. Aired: 11/07/91-12/20/91. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 865)
  - Prod. #1190-1217. Aired: 12/23/91-01/31/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 866)
  - Prod. #1118-1247. Aired: 02/03/92-03/15/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1236). (Box 867)
  - Prod. #1248-1280. Aired: 03/16/92-05/02/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1270). (Box 868)
  - Prod. #1281-1310. Aired: 05/05/92-06/15/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 869)
  - Prod. #1311-1340. Aired: 06/16/92-07/27/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 870)
  - Prod. #1341-1370. Aired: 07/28/92-09/08/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 871)
  - Prod. #1371-1402. Aired: 09/09/92-10/23/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1375,1385). (Box 872)
  - Prod. #1403-1439. Aired: 10/27/92-12/16/92. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1403,1408-1412,1422,1426). (Box 873)
  - Prod. #1440-1470. Aired: 12/17/92-02/02/93. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 874)
  - Prod. #1471-1503. Aired: 02/03/93-03/23/93. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS. (Box 875)
  - Prod. #1504-1537. Aired: 03/24/93-05/11/93. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1536). (Box 876)
  - Prod. #264-685. Aired:. Notes: Brief summaries. (Box 877)
  - Prod. #1538-1558. Aired: 05/11/93-06/08/93. Notes: SCRIPTS/DRAFTS (Missing #1553,1554). (Box 877)
- DAYS OF OUR LIVES
  - Prod. #1367-1396. Aired: 04/07/71-05/18/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 1)
  - Prod. #1397-1426. Aired: 05/19/71-06/29/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 2)
  - Prod. #1427-1456. Aired: 06/30/71-08/10/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 3)
  - Prod. #1457-1486. Aired: 08/11/71-09/22/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 4)
  - Prod. #1487-1511. Aired: 09/23/71-(TAPE)10/19/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 5)
  - Prod. #2802-2816. Aired: 12/29/76-11/18/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 6)
  - Prod. #2817-2829. Aired: 01/19/77-02/03/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 7)
  - Prod. #2830-2839. Aired: 02/10/77-02/11/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 8)
  - Prod. #2840-2851. Aired: 02/25/77-03/07/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 9)
  - Prod. #2852-2860. Aired: 03/08/77-03/22/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 10)
  - Prod. #1535-1607. Aired: 12/09/71-03/21/72. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 11)
  - Prod. #1608-1685. Aired: 03/22/72-07/11/72. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 12)
  - Prod. #1686-1759. Aired: 07/12/72-10/25/72. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 13)
  - Prod. #1760-1829. Aired: 10/26/72-02/08/73. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 14)
  - Prod. #1830-1892. Aired: 02/11/73-05/07/73. Notes: SCRIPTS AND OUTLINES. (Box 15)
  - Prod. #1222-1246. Aired: 09/08/70-10/12/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 16)
  - Prod. #1247-1276. Aired: 10/13/70-11/30/70. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 17)
  - Prod. #1277-1306. Aired: 12/01/70-01/11/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 18)
  - Prod. #1307-1336. Aired: 11/12/71-02/22/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 19)
  - Prod. #1337-1366. Aired: 02/23/71-04/06/71. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 20)
  - Prod. #1809-1838. Aired: 01/09/73-02/22/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 21)
  - Prod. #1839-1868. Aired: 02/23/73-04/05/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 22)
  - Prod. #1869-1899. Aired: 04/06/73-05/18/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 23)
  - Prod. #1900-1929. Aired: 05/21/73-(TAPE)06/21/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 24)
  - Prod. #1930-1959. Aired: (TAPE)06/22/73-08/17/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 25)
  - Prod. #2998-3013. Aired: 09/30/77-10/18/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 26)
  - Prod. #3014-3025. Aired: 10/24/77-11/08/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 27)
  - Prod. #3029-3033. Aired: 11/14/77-11/18/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 28)
  - Prod. #3035-3043. Aired: 11/22/77-12/02/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 28)
  - Prod. #3044-3053. Aired: 12/05/77-12/16/77. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 29)
  - Prod. #2115-2144. Aired: 04/22/74-05/31/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 30)
  - Prod. #2145-2174. Aired: 06/03/74-07/12/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 31)
  - Prod. #2175-2204. Aired: 07/15/74-08/23/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 32)
  - Prod. #2205-2234. Aired: 08/26/74-10/07/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 33)
  - Prod. #2235-2259. Aired: 10/04/74-11/12/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 34)
  - Prod. #2260-2289. Aired: 11/14/74-12/25/74. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 35)
  - Prod. #2290-2319. Aired: 12/26/74-02/10/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 36)
  - Prod. #2320-2349. Aired: 02/12/75-03/23/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 37)
  - Prod. #2350-2370. Aired: 03/26/75-04/24/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 38)
  - Prod. #2371-2385. Aired: 04/25/75-05/15/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 39)
  - Prod. #2521-2533. Aired: 11/25/75-12/15/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 40)
  - Prod. #2534-2545. Aired: 12/16/75-12/30/75. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 41)
  - Prod. #2546-2557. Aired: 12/31/75-11/06/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 42)
  - Prod. #2558-2569. Aired: 01/19/76-02/04/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 43)
  - Prod. #2570-2581. Aired: 02/05/76-02/20/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 44)
  - Prod. #2582-2587. Aired: 02/23/76-03/01/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 45)
  - Prod. #3054-3068. Aired: 12/19/77-01/09/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 46)
  - Prod. #3069-3083. Aired: 01/10/78-01/30/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 47)
  - Prod. #3084-3099. Aired: 01/31/78-02/21/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 48)
  - Prod. #3100-3114. Aired: 02/22/78-03/14/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 49)
  - Prod. #3115-3129. Aired: 03/15/78-04/04/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 50)
  - Prod. #3130-3137. Aired: 04/05/78-04/15/78. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 51)
  - Prod. #1661-1692. Aired: 06/07/72-07/20/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 52)
  - Prod. #1693-1722. Aired: 07/21/72-09/04/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 53)
  - Prod. #1723-1752. Aired: 09/05/72-10/16/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 54)
  - Prod. #1753-1783. Aired: 10/17/72-12/04/72. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 55)
  - Prod. #1784-1808. Aired: 12/05/72-01/08/73. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 56)
  - Prod. #2733-2746. Aired: 09/22/76-10/11/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 57)
  - Prod. #2747-2760. Aired: 10/12/76-10/29/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 58)
  - Prod. #2761-2775. Aired: 11/01/76-11/19/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 59)
  - Prod. #2776-2789. Aired: 11/22/76-12/10/76. Notes: SCRIPTS. (Box 60)